hello guy welcome back to my channel we
end up there today I'm going to show you
how the difference in Cambodia about
life insurance because many of us start
to understand about life insurance more
and more the insurance company started
from zero but now many people start to
use the insurance
so I'm going to read you a new we are
talking about like engine for today
Cambodians clamors for life innocence
cross premium in the insurance industry
which 140 2.9 million dollars last year
26 percent rise on the figure of one
hundred and thirteen point five million
dollars the year before according to
Denton's Association of Cambodia IAC in
the 2017 general insurance experienced
moderate grow of seven percent to about
seventy five point four million dollars
compared with 2010 sexing however cross
life insurance premiums reach sixty
point five million last year a 50 sec
person from the two thousand and safety
of forty three point 1 million dollars
the rights of cross premiums in the
insurance industry demonstrates
increasing demand from Cambodians for
financial and risk management solutions
and incb forces I am chairman we said
the success of the reasons industry had
been significantly bolstered by the
country's stable economic growth and
increasing demand for protection as more
Cambodians understood the concept of
insurance
I'm very excited to witness the industry
grow throughout the past years
especially in 2017 when the number of
insurers operating camera crew to
thirteen six of which are from the still
new life insurance industry which
started in 2012 accept the presence of
these insurance companies has a very
positive impact on society the risk
mitigation job creation talent
development in the instrument sector and
many more ways robot elite AIC vice
chairman and CEO of Manulife highlighted
the positive impact that the life
insulins industry had met on Cambodians
throughout 2017 s life coverage Ross
deli and we're excited to see the life
insurance industry crew wing in line
with the Racine life
Livingston lot of the people as well as
the fast growing economic of Cambodia he
said last year to new life interests
joined the market and international 1786
thousand new life insurance policies
were issued to Cambodia being families
with a total Sangha Shu
of 2.5 billion dollars the equivalent to
more than 60 percent increase on 2016
mr. Elliott said if something happens to
lives in sir in suit their family will
get the son a suit so that they won't
face a financial burden mr. butell
added that the development of a good
regulatory framework for the incidence
industry also played an important part
in the health tick road of life and
non-life business in Cambodia yeah so as
we know where that life is ready